【The fate that cannot be liberated】
【无法解脱的命运】
[Episode 12]
[第12集]
stop.
停止。
go.
去。
They started arresting people again
他们又开始抓人了
[Wanted Order]
[通缉令]
What crime did they commit?
他们犯了什么罪？
go.
去。
sorry.
对不起。
I can not help you.
我帮不了你。
I can only tell you
我只能告诉你
running.
跑步。
Run as far as you can.
跑得尽可能远。
If someone wants to point fingers, excuses will always be found.
如果有人想指责， 总是会找到借口。
No one can save you.
没有人能拯救你。
get away!
逃离！
try your best.
尽你所能。
Let's go now!
现在就走吧！
What's wrong?
怎么了？
are you afraid of dying
你害怕死去吗
Father and our brothers?
父亲和我们的兄弟？
Jiuling,
Jiuling,
I'm not afraid.
我不怕。
You will be the only one of our family to survive .
你将是我们家族中唯一幸存的人 。
What are we doing here?
我们在这里做什么？
- He San. Hesan. - WHO?
-何三。何三. - WHO？
hurry. He is a fugitive from the He family.
匆忙。是何家的逃亡者。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Why did you come to Rong Mansion blatantly?
为何明目张胆的来荣府？
When you see the jade pendant, it's like seeing the emperor.
当你看到玉佩时， 就好像你看到了皇帝。
You are just guardians.
你们只是守护者。
how dare you!
你怎么敢！
Aren't you afraid of offending the emperor?
就不怕得罪皇上吗？
All of you, stay out of my way.
你们所有人都别挡我的路。
This dragon pendant can only be effective for a period of time.
这龙坠只能发挥一段时间的作用。
A moment is enough.
一会儿就够了。
Rong Yu.
Rong Yu.
come out. Jiuling is here to see you.
出来。九灵来看你了。
Master, please have some soup.
少爷，请喝汤。
Rong Yu.
Rong Yu.
He Jiuling is here to see you.
贺九菱来看你了。
He San, put me down.
何三，放我下来。
Rong Yu.
Rong Yu.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
what's wrong with you?
你这人怎么回事？
He San,
何三,
What are you doing?
你到底在做什么？
where are they.
他们在哪里。
hurry up.
赶快。
Master Rong.
荣师傅。
I will entrust Jiuling to you from now on, okay?
以后我就把九灵托付给你了，好吗？
Marry Jiuling now.
现在就和九龄结婚吧。
Do you want me to get married at a time like this?
你想让我在这种时候结婚吗？
Jiuling,
Jiuling,
We have no choice now.
我们现在别无选择。
But what does it matter?
但是，这有什么关系
Am I getting married?
我是否结婚？
The He family is guilty,
何家人有罪，
But it should not affect outsiders.
但不应该影响到外人。
outsider?
局外人？
They are in the young master's yard. hurry up!
他们就在少爷的院子里。 赶快！
hurry up.
赶快。
They are in the young master's yard.
他们就在少爷的院子里。
open the door. hurry up!
打开门。赶快！
So, you don’t want me to become a member of the He family?
所以，你不想让我 成为何家的人了？
I don't.
我不。
hurry. Open the door!
匆忙。开门！
Capture them and execute them immediately.
抓住他们并立即处决他们。
The young master is inside. Don't hurt him.
少爷就在里面。别伤害他。
go. hurry. Open the door!
去。匆忙。开门！
He Qiuting, who do you think you are?
何秋婷，你以为你是谁？
What right do you have to prevent me from entering the He family?
你有什么权利 不让我进入贺家？
What qualifications do you have to marry me into the Rong family?
你有什么资格 把我嫁给荣家？
Because I am your brother.
因为我是你的兄弟。
Jiuling,
Jiuling,
You never considered me your brother,
你从来没有把我当作你的兄弟，
You never called me brother either.
你也从来没有叫过我兄弟。
But my father and brothers are not here,
但父亲和哥哥们都不在这里，
You must listen to me.
你必须听我的。
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
Regarding past marriage contracts,
关于过去的婚姻契约，
It's our fault.
这是我们的错。
We owe you an apology.
我们欠你一个道歉。
Do you still want to
你还想吗
spend the rest of your life
度过余生
Together with He Jiuling, we will never be separated again?
和何九菱在一起，​​再也不分开？
Open the door!
开门！
Then you kneel with her now in front of heaven and earth
那么你现在就和她一起跪 在天地面前
Is it okay to marry her?
娶她为妻，可以吗？
I do not want.
我不想。
hurry. Turn it on!
匆忙。把它打开！
open the door. Turn it on. hurry up!
打开门。把它打开。赶快！
open the door. hurry. open the door.
打开门。匆忙。打开门。
He San.
何三.
open the door.
打开门。
Jiuling,
Jiuling,
I once told you,
我曾经告诉过你，
If you want to rob, I will help you dispose of the stolen goods.
如果你想抢劫， 我就帮你处理掉赃物。
If you want to steal flowers, I will spy on you.
如果你想偷花， 我会监视你。
If you want to kill someone, I will hide the body for you.
如果你想杀人， 我会帮你把尸体藏起来。
But now you are going to be killed
但现在你就要被杀了
I'll block your way.
我会挡住你的路。
I'm so useless.
我太没用了。
I couldn't save my father.
我无法拯救父亲。
I can't save my brother and sister-in-law.
我救不了哥哥 、嫂子。
He San!
何三！
I can at least save you.
我至少可以救你。
Today is my sister's wedding.
今天是我姐姐的婚礼。
Welcome to the ceremony.
欢迎参加仪式。
catch him!
抓住他！
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
Please take good care of Jiuling.
求你好好照顾九灵。
She always thinks she is smart
她总觉得自己很聪明
But she is actually very naive.
但她其实很天真。
And her willpower is particularly strong.
而且她的意志力特别坚强。
No matter how much pain she has, how painful it is,
不管她有多痛， 有多痛，
She won't cry for herself.
她不会为自己哭泣。
Her will is so strong.
她的意志是如此坚强。
She only shed tears for you
她只为你流过泪
in the past.
在过去。
Don't make her cry again.
以后不要再让她哭了。
Master.
少爷。
What does it matter if she is wanted by the courts?
如果她被法庭通缉又有什么关系呢？
do you really want her to die
你真的想让她死吗
Make the young master sad?
让少爷伤心？
-Jiu Ling. - Stay out of my way.
-九龄。 - 别挡我的路。
This is very dangerous. Stop the young master from coming forward.
这是非常危险的。 阻止少爷上前。
- Young master. - Jiuling.
- Young master. - Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Jiuling. Jiuling.
Jiuling. Jiuling.
You will be the only one of our family to survive .
你将是我们家族中唯一幸存的人 。
Don't let my death be in vain.
别让我白白死去。
I beg you.
我求求你。
Kneel down for you.
给你跪下来。
hurry up.
赶快。
Kowtow first.
先磕头。
Master, hurry up. Kneel down with Miss He.
少爷，快点。跟何小姐一起跪下。
To heaven and earth.
至天地。
Kowtow for the second time.
第二次磕头。
To my brothers.
致兄弟们。
Master, hurry up.
少爷，快点。
Father. Father. Father.
父亲。父亲。父亲。
- I will kill you - Father.
- 我会杀了你 - 父亲。
Dad, if you leave her with a scar, my brother-in-law will ask for a return.
爸爸，如果你给她留下了伤疤， 我姐夫会要求退货的。
Father, stop being confused. Father.
父亲，你别再糊涂了。父亲。
Father.
父亲。
How would you like to style your hair?
您想如何设计您的头发？
I'm going to study.
我去学习一下。
From now on, you can sit here every morning
从现在开始， 你每天早上就可以坐在这里
I'll comb your hair.
我会为你梳理头发。
Third brother!
三哥！
Anyway, I helped you with something.
无论如何，我帮了你一件事。
When siblings work together, their power can cut through metal.
当兄弟姐妹齐心协力时， 他们的力量可以穿透金属。
I will definitely protect you.
我一定会保护你的。
Make sure you are happy and carefree.
确保你快乐、无忧无虑。
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Get He Jiuling.
Get He Jiuling.
Yes.
是的。
The young master and young lady have just completed the ceremony.
少爷少夫人 刚刚完成了仪式。
Who dares to harm the young lady?
谁敢害少夫人？
You can't take my wife away.
你不能带走我的妻子。
Master, your marriage is just child's play.
少爷， 你的婚姻只是儿戏。
Zhan Ping said, the ceremony is completed and we are husband and wife.
展平说，仪式完成了， 我们就是夫妻了。
You can't take my wife away.
你不能带走我的妻子。
The He family was sentenced to genocide.
何氏家族被判处灭族。
Even if you are married,
就算你已经结婚了，
This still happened after the verdict.
判决后仍然发生了这种情况。
He Jiuling must be taken away by order of the Ministry of Punishment.
必须奉刑部之令将贺九龄带走。
Don't you think she can be acquitted?
你不认为她可以被无罪释放吗
By dishonest measures.
通过不诚实的措施。
Yong adult,
容大人，
do you agree?
你同意？
uncle.
叔叔。
Then you should take me with you.
那你也该带上我吧。
I am already married to He Jiuling.
我已经和何九龄结婚了。
I am also a member of the He family now.
我现在也是何家的人了。
Well.
呃。
Lord of Song Dynasty.
宋主。
Yes.
是的。
They did get married in a hurry.
他们确实匆忙结婚了。
But the engagement was already set.
但订婚早已定下。
He Jiuling is from the Rong family.
何九龄是荣氏家族的人。
She shouldn't bear the sins of the He family.
贺家的罪孽，她不该承受。
Yong adult,
容大人，
Why are you so confused?
你怎么会这么困惑？
Back then, He Jiuling ran off to Nanjiang.
Back then, He Jiuling ran off to Nanjiang.
Everyone knows
谁都知道
She is running away from marriage.
她正在逃避婚姻。
Now she's taking advantage of the engagement
现在，她正在利用婚约
Save her life.
救她的命。
How heartless she is.
她多么无情啊。
How could you let her do this!
你怎么可以让她这么做！
So, do you also want to take Yu with you?
那么，你也想带上宇一起去吗？
I will never take the young master with me.
我是绝对不会带少爷的。
He was just acting impulsively now.
他现在只是一时冲动而已。
after a while,
一段时间后，
He would definitely forget her.
他肯定会忘记她的。
I'm afraid he won't.
恐怕他不会。
Zhanping, go take care of Heshan.
Zhanping, go take care of Heshan.
I will take care of her.
我会照顾她的。
Do not be afraid.
别害怕。
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
General He,
何将军，
He Qiuting passed away.
何秋婷去世了。
This is where he belongs.
这是他的归属。
You can get this before executing.
你可以在执行之前得到这个。
Father, what did he just say?
父亲，他刚才说什么？
Qiuting, what happened to Qiuting?
秋婷，秋婷怎么了？
dd-Did he say that?
dd-他说了吗
Did he run away?
他逃跑了？
this child
这孩子
Usually timid and afraid of pain.
通常胆小怕痛。
He's not good at anything
他什么都不擅长
But run away.
但逃跑。
Fortunately he escaped.
还好他逃了。
I always knew he could escape.
我一直都知道他可以逃跑。
Master, stop covering up for her.
少爷，别再包庇她了。
The little madam has already covered herself with so many quilts.
小夫人 已经盖了这么多被子了。
If you cover her again, she will suffocate.
如果你再盖住她，她就会窒息。
But her hands were so cold.
但她的手好冷。
I'll get her a hand warmer.
我会给她准备一个暖手器。
The hand warmer is too hot.
暖手宝太热了。
The young master knew that he would always hold her like this.
小少爷 就知道一直这样抱着她。
Then holding her like this all the time is the right thing to do.
那么一直这样抱着她 才是正确的做法。
The quilt is too stuffy.
被子太闷了。
You will suffocate her, Master.
你会窒息她的，少爷。
Okay then.
那么好吧。
Master,
少爷，
tt-Today is not a good day.
tt-今天不是个好日子。
I wonder if the young lady will wake up?
不知道少夫人会不会醒过来呢？
By noon,
到了中午的时候，
I'm going to pick up her family? ? ?
我去接她的家人？？？
what time is it now?
现在几点了？
- young lady. you're awake! - you're awake!
- 年轻的女士。你醒了！ - 你醒了！
Prepare the horse.
准备马。
Yang Ying.
Yang Ying.
sorry.
对不起。
If there is another life
如果还有下辈子的话
I want to love you passionately.
我想热烈地爱你。
You just need to say it once a day.
你只需要每天说一遍。
I love you.
我爱你。
Then he will be beautiful
这样他就会很漂亮
It’s a pleasure to be your child.
很高兴成为您的孩子。
Brother, you have to say this too.
大哥，这话你也得说啊。
No, I can not.
不，我不能。
Say it.
说吧。
I love you.
我爱你。
I love you too.
我也爱你。
[Order]
[命令]
implement.
执行。
Stop the carriage.
停下马车。
Flatten and park.
展平，停车吧。
A loyal soul never dies,
忠诚的灵魂永不消亡，
Waiting for the day of justice.
等待平反的那一天。
bid farewell,
告别，
Father.
父亲。
Father!
父亲！
My lovely daughter!
我可爱的女儿！
Goodbye, brother and sister-in-law.
再见了，大哥和大嫂。
How cute!
多可爱！
Goodbye, second brother and second sister-in-law.
再见，二哥、二嫂。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Come on, I'm here.
来吧，我在这里。
I'm not afraid of you.
我不怕你。
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
??? 黄昏夕阳下？？？
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
??? 我千里迢迢去远方？？？
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
??? 月下弹琴？？？
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
??? 这些饮料不会让我忘记？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满了？？？
???With joy and sadness? ? ?
??? 带着喜悦和悲伤？？？
???Eager for crystallization? ? ?
??? 渴望结晶？？？
???Into the bright Milky Way? ? ?
??? 进入明亮的银河系？？？
???I gently stroke the guzheng? ? ?
??? 我轻轻抚摸古筝？？？
???Waiting for a passerby like you? ? ?
??? 等一个和你一样的路人？？？
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
??? 原来你就是我的不解之缘？？？
【Rongfu】 ? ? ? So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
【荣府】 ？？？原来你就是我的不解之缘？？？
I am fine.
我很好。
this is yours.
这是你的。
Keep it for now.
暂时保留吧。
Master.
少爷。
Today we are going to the astrology center. Don't forget it.
今天我们要去占星馆。 别忘了它。
Astrology Garden
占星馆花园
More beautiful than here.
比这里更美丽。
The wintersweet flowers bloom particularly well there.
那里的腊梅花开得特别好。
Heshan said, these are all
鹤山说，这些都是
I planted it.
是我种的。
Do you want to go see them?
你想去看看他们吗？
It's not snowing outside.
外面没下雪。
There are some shops open on the street.
街上有一些商店开门营业。
Master, it will be too late if you don’t leave now.
少爷， 你现在再不走就晚了。
When you want to go out,
当你想出去的时候，
Just tell me.
就告诉我嘛。
Madam, the prince wants to see you.
少夫人，王爷要见您。
young lady.
年轻的女士。
I should be the one paying homage to you.
应该是我向你致敬。
I should also apologize.
我也应该道歉。
I will never forget your kindness
我永远不会忘记你的恩情
He saved my third brother that day.
那天救了我的三弟。
Why are you? ? ?
你为什么？？？
The prince has dismissed my young master from the position of personal bodyguard.
王爷已经解除了我 少爷贴身侍卫的职务。
He wants me to leave Rongfu
他要我离开荣府
And never set foot on it again.
并且再也没有踏足过它。
leave?
离开？
I'll tell the young master and Zhanping
我去告诉少爷和展平
I will go back to visit my family.
我会回去看望我的家人。
So please keep my secret, young lady.
所以请为我保守秘密，年轻的女士。
And after that?
之后呢？
Things will get better after that.
之后事情会好起来的。
I'm just an insignificant person.
我只是一个微不足道的人。
no one will remember me
没有人会记得我
after a while.
一段时间后。
Loss and gain.
损失与收获。
Meeting and parting.
相遇与离别。
This happens all the time.
这种事经常发生。
Don't blame yourself, young lady.
别责怪自己，年轻的女士。
Nor do you ask for mercy from the Lord.
亦勿向主求情。
Otherwise, the situation could be worse.
否则，情况可能会更糟。
Just keep it a secret for me.
只为我保守秘密。
get.
获得。
loss.
损失。
Meeting.
会议。
parting.
离别。
This happens often
这种事经常发生
Only suitable for acquaintances.
只适合熟人。
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Now you are alone.
现在你孤身一人了。
If you can never fully commit to anyone again,
如果你再也无法完全委身于任何人，
You will never experience loss and separation.
你永远不会经历失落和分离。
【Remember forever】
【永远铭记】
I heard that your left hand hurts again.
听说你的左手又疼了。
Suffered minor injuries. This is not a problem.
受了轻伤。这不是一个问题。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
I invite you to come here today
我今天请你到这里来
Remind you of something.
提醒你某事。
I allow you to marry Rong Yu
我允许你嫁给容羽
So you should follow the rules here.
所以你应该遵守这里的规则。
When your elders advise you, you should kneel down.
当长辈劝告时，你应该跪下。
[Rong Zhizhi’s Lingpai]
【容芝芝的灵牌】
As a wife,
身为妻子，
You should prioritize your husband.
你应该优先考虑你的丈夫。
If your husband doesn't come back,
如果你的丈夫没有回来，
You shouldn't eat or sleep first.
你不应该先吃饭或睡觉。
When your husband is at home,
当你老公在家的时候，
you should take care of him
你应该照顾他
And worried about his worries.
并担心他的忧虑。
You shouldn't let him worry about you.
你不应该让他为你担心。
do you understand?
你明白吗？
Yes.
是的。
when he is sick,
当他生病时，
You should sleep in separate beds.
你们应该睡在不同的床上。
now,
如今，
Rong Yu sleeps separately from you.
容羽和你分开睡。
but i think
但我觉得
people sleeping outside
睡在外面的人
It shouldn't be Rong Yu, right?
应该不会是容羽吧？
We'll switch back tonight.
今晚我们将切换回来。
I don't care if you used to practice martial arts.
我不在乎 你过去是否习武。
but now,
但现在，
Rong Yu's body is very weak.
容羽的身体很虚弱。
He couldn't stand this.
他无法忍受这样的事情。
Put your sword away.
把你的剑收起来。
Forget...
把...忘了吧
All martial arts things.
所有武术的事情。
As for the He family’s affairs,
至于何家的事情，
this is your wealth
这是你的财富
Survive.
生存。
from now on,
今后，
Just be the young lady you are.
就当你年轻的女士吧。
if i knew
如果我知道
You are not willing to live your own life,
你不甘心自己的生活，
I will punish you with house rules.
我会用家规惩罚你。
I'll give you some lessons from women.
我会给你一些女性的教诲。
You have to copy them a hundred times first.
你必须先把它们复制一百遍。
Yes.
是的。
in a few days,
在几天内，
Mr. Song from the Ministry of Justice will hold a promotion banquet.
法务部宋大人 将举行晋升宴会。
Rong Yu and you will attend and bring some gifts
容宇和你将出席 并带一些礼物
Represents the Rong family and Xingxiang Pavilion.
代表荣家 和星象阁。
Yes.
是的。
【Astrology Center】
【占星馆】
The sky is blue and the earth is yellow.
天空是蓝色的，大地是黄色的。
The universe is boundless and time is boundless.
宇宙无边无际 ，时间无边无际。
The sun rises and sets. The moon is round and waning.
太阳升起和落下。 月亮有圆有缺。
The sky is full of stars.
天空布满了星星。
Master, it’s time for you to turn the page.
少爷，你该翻页了。
OK
好的。
That’s it for today.
今天就到这里吧。
Be sure to imitate the copybook carefully after returning home.
回家后一定要仔细模仿字帖。
Next time we will learn new characters.
下次我们会学习新的角色。
School is out. School is out. School is out.
学校放学了。学校放学了。学校放学了。
It's time to go home. Master. Master. Master.
该回家了。 少爷。少爷。少爷。
Master.
少爷。
Try this.
尝尝这个。
How do you give him cakes?
你怎么给他糕点
Did you take a bite?
你咬了一口吗？
I really can't resist
我真的无法抗拒
During class.
上课期间。
Master, have you learned all the Chinese characters in today’s lesson?
少爷，今天课的汉字你都学会了吗？
Then there is no need to worry. I do not have either.
那么就不用担心了。我也没有。
Master, I studied very hard today.
少爷，我今天学习很努力。
Can you reward me with my head?
你能奖励一下我的头吗？
Me too. Me too.
我也是。我也是。
I also want to take a photo
我也想拍拍
Well, I don't have time to play with you today.
好吧，我今天没时间陪你玩。
I want to go back to be with my wife.
我要回去陪我老婆。
Why does your wife need company?
为什么你的妻子需要陪伴？
Yes, why?
是的，为什么？
because,
因为，
Because she is unhappy.
因为她不开心。
You can cheer her up with some candied hawthorn.
你可以用一些蜜饯山楂让她高兴起来。
You can also buy her a pet cricket.
你也可以给她买一只宠物蟋蟀。
Are you a dummy?
你是傻子吗？
We are fortune tellers.
我们是算命师。
We should use the methods learned in Astrology Pavilion to solve this problem.
我们应该用在占星阁学到的方法来解决这个问题。
Master, do you know when your wife’s birthday is?
少爷， 你知道你妻子的生日是什么时候吗？
I'll ask my dad to give your wife a prediction.
我让我爸爸给你老婆预测一下
See if there is any way to solve the wife's problem.
看看有没有办法 解决妻子的问题。
Little brother, this is not my wife.
小兄弟，这不是老婆。
She is the young master's wife.
她是少爷的妻子。
We should call her the young lady.
我们应该称呼她为少夫人。
So, when is our young lady’s birthday?
那么，我们少夫人的生日是什么时候呢？
She is not our young lady.
她不是我们的少夫人。
She is the young master's young wife.
她是少爷的少夫人。
It was December 22nd of the sixth year of Zhenyuan.
时值贞元六年十二月二十二日。
Isn’t there still three days left?
不是还有三天吗？
Leave the divination to me.
占卜就交给我吧。
Master, isn't this a good opportunity?
少爷，这不是一个很好的机会吗？
Are you ready for a fun birthday gift?
你准备好有趣的生日礼物了吗
Make her happy?
让她开心？
Yes Yes.
是的是的。
birthday present?
生日礼物？
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
??? 黄昏夕阳下？？？
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
??? 我千里迢迢去远方？？？
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
??? 月下弹琴？？？
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
??? 这些饮料不会让我忘记？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 你悄悄转身 合上了婚书？？？
???Ask how many stars are there in the sky? ? ?
??? 问天上有多少颗星星？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???I gently caress the guzheng, waiting for passers-by like you???
??? 我轻轻抚着古筝， 等待着你这样的路人???
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
??? 原来你就是我的不解之缘？？？